In this video, I'm going to show you how
to use unlimited vibe code with cursor
and claude code. So, you're going to be
able to use the unlimited for free with
the latest models. By the end of this
video, I'm going to show you how to set
everything up with no technical
knowledge and no credit card. I'm also
going to show you how to create a
website from start to finish. I've
created hundreds of websites and I'm
going to show you the best way how.
You're going to want to watch all the
way to the end. Leave a like, subscribe,
and turn post notifications on if you
haven't yet. Anybody can use this video.
I'm going to try to make this the most
useful video on YouTube for vibe coding.
You don't need a credit card. You don't
need technical experience and the best
way I know how from just trial and error
and just from expertise of just learning
along the way. I know you guys enjoy my
previous videos about Vibe Coding. So, I
want to create a follow-up video for you
guys to continue on in the Vibe Code
journey. Any links that I mentioned in
here, put all of the links in the
description down below for your
reference as well. First off, go to
google.com, type in ravoev. So, ro ov e
v. Once you're here, you're going to
click on the first link. You don't need
a credit card. Everything in this video
is completely for free. So you're here.
You're going to click on try it now. It
says work email, but you can enter any
email you want. For me, I like to use
Gmail. So for example, this is one
email, right? After the trial up and you
want to do another one, you just do a
dot. So this is a new email. And then
you want to do another email dot. So
this is just kind of like a email people
do to get unlimited Gmails. So we're
going to sign up for a account right
now. You can see here the green. And
then I'm going to click sign up. You'll
be presented with this screen. Next up,
you're going to go to your email and
then get the code that they just sent
you. So, I'm going to go to my email and
get the code. So, when you're in your
email, you'll see a code like this. And
you can see here that I have the code.
All you got to do is take that code,
right click, copy, go back to that
window, paste that code in, and then
after that, you'll see it's email
address verified. And then for here, you
just enter any name. And then for the
password, you enter literally any
password. Press continue. Next up,
you're presented with the screen. For
your site name, you have to enter
anything. Just pick something random
that's available. And then when you see
it is green on and then I put agree and
start. Now you'll get presented with
this window. Once it is successfully
loaded, you'll get presented with this
like tutorial thing. Just click X. You
don't really need it. And then when
you're here, you're going to click on
Bravo Dev CLI. Next up, we're going to
install Bravo Dev CLI. If you have a
Mac, click on Mac. If you have a
Windows, click on Windows. If you have a
Linux, click on Linux. Right now, we're
using a Mac, so we're going to click on
Mac. You can see here that it opened a
new window. Next up, you're going to
open up your terminal. Take this first
link. Copy. Go to your terminal, paste
it in, press enter, and you can see here
that it's successfully installed. I
already had it installed, so it's just
turned to updating, but for you, it will
show something similar. Next up, you're
going to click the second link right
here, brew install ACL. Go back to that
same terminal. Ctrl +V, copy and paste
it in, press enter. From there, there
you go. Once you see it pop back to this
empty spot, then you'll know it's
successfully installed. If you make sure
you check for this third one, this is a
command that check the version you have.
copy ACL live space- version. Go back to
your terminal, press enter, and it
should say some type of version, but for
you, it'll be whatever version in the
current time you're watching it in. So,
it's continually updating. Now, we can
go back to our web browser. We can close
this window. Next, we're going to
generate an API token. Click that link.
You can see here that another
verification code has been sent to your
email. So, go back to the email that you
originally used earlier. You take that
code from the email, you go back to that
page, and then you press Ctrl +V and
paste it in. Next, you'll be presented
with this window. Click on create API
token. For the name, name it anything
you want. For the date, choose any date
you want. Typically, I see it last about
you'll be able to vibe code for about 6
hours and then you'll just create a new
one and you then you'll get another 20
million credits again. And you just keep
doing it and it's pretty much just
unlimited vibe coding. So, we pick a
date in the future. We picked any name
we want and we press create and then you
can see here that successfully
generated. In the terminal, you're going
to type in a space ravo dev space off
space logout. and you'll see log out
successfully. This is the step that you
would do if you've pre previously used
of the trial again and you want to use
another new trial. All you have to do is
log out. So you can see I'm logged out
successfully of my old trial. Next,
you're going to type in a CLI base robot
dev off base log in. You'll see the
email. This is the email that you used
previously. So I'm going to input my
email. Then when here press enter and
then it's going to say enter your API
token. So this is just go back to your
window. This is just the one that we
created. Click on copy and you can see
API token copy to clipboard. Go back to
your terminal, paste it in, press enter,
and once you see the authentification
successful, this means that everything
is completely set up for you to vibe
code unlimitedly. If you redo this
process over again, you'll be you'll
have a brand new account, fresh tokens.
Again, this was the part of how to set
up Ravo Dev and how to get all the
features of Claude code and cursor
completely for free. Next up, I'm going
to show you how to create a website from
start to finish. So, we go back here. If
you want to save this as well, this is
just pretty much how to log in. And this
is just pretty much how to run it. So
you pretty much once you open up in any
folder you you type in this command
right here and then you press enter. And
when you type it in and press enter it
opens up the CLI which I will show you
next. Let's create the website. So go
open up your terminal type in cd and
then type in the brand new directory
that you want to show. So to create a
brand new directory what I'm going to do
is this. I opened up a brand new folder.
Right click new folder. We'll name this
directory tech Kevin website. And you
can see that in the in the terminal I
typed in cd. I'm literally just going to
drag and drop. You can do this on
Windows as well. Next on your terminal,
you'll see that we're currently in the
directory of tech cabin website. This
literally is just an empty folder right
now, right? We're going to type in ACL
ACL space ravo dev space run. When this
pops up, just click allow. And then you
can see that once we're in here, we can
see that everything successfully set up
and we have access to all of the latest
models. The slash icon and then you'll
be presented with a bunch of different
options. Click the dash and then you're
going to go down to yolo. You're going
to go down to yolo. Press enter. And
once you can see yolo is engaged. What
this does is it pretty much skips on all
the confirmations and just vibe codes
all the way to the end. If you click
here, you can also clear the window. And
then you can also go down. There's
different options as well. You can
clear, you can copy, you can go to
different directories, manage it, you
can go feedback, help, IDE, MCP servers
if you have that. You can also do
memory. And if you go down to models,
you can change the models. So, they
currently have GPT 5, which is the
latest GBT. They have the latest Sonnet
as well, 4.5. Okay, since we're in the
directory, I'll show you guys how to
create a brand new website now. And so,
since we have everything set up right
now, the prompt I'm going to type in is
create me a React website. I added a
image folder with a template screenshot.
It's not going to come be perfect, but
it's going to be something pretty nice.
I want you to create me a website
exactly similar to the UX of that. You
press enter. See that right now it's
successfully vibe coding. I I'm using
GPT5. And then we're going to create the
React website right now. And make sure
you type in that prompt exactly like
kind of how it is. Say create me a React
website. So because if you say create a
website just in general it might just do
basic different text stack you know but
using the react I'm telling it to create
me a react website and we just wait for
it to do its magic and you can pretty
much just do this unlimitedly you can
create any sort of website you can
create any sort of app any sort of
software it can do you can ask it
questions you can use it kind of like
cloud pro or chat tbt pro and just ask
it questions okay guys so it looks like
it finished when it's done you'll see
something like this towards the end. It
says your React website. So, you can see
here that we just created a sample
website. And then we're just going to go
here. We're going to copy and paste that
localhost that colon 3000. And it's it's
pretty quick, right? And we're going to
go back to our web browser. We're going
to paste it in localhost colon thing um
3000. Wow. And this is that we just
created right now. So, this is just
literally one prompt, a single prompt
that we that we pasted it in and we
literally created this entire just one
page right now. But we can create more
pages. This is just one prompt as well.
So I'm actually pretty amazed by this.
And you can see here literally from one
prompt this was the result. You can see
here this is a local this is not a live
website. We but we can host it live
later. That's it for the video. I hope
you guys enjoyed. Let me know what you
think. Please leave a like, subscribe,
turn post notifications on. I'll see you
guys again in the next video. Peace out.